=His Chosen Favor=
=مفضلته المختارة=
(If You Dare Touch My Person, You're Dead)
(إن تجرأت على لمس جسدي، فأنت ميت)
=Episode 8=
=الحلقة 8=
Xiao Yicheng.
شياو ييتشنغ.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
how dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Tell me. Where is Lu Zhen'er?
أخبرني، أين لو تشن إير؟
You want her dead.
تريد موتها.
Why do you even care about her life?
لماذا تهتم بحياتها أصلاً؟
Hand over Lu Zhen'er.
تسليم لو Zhen'er.
Or I'll castrate you, a depraved prince who slept with an imperial consort.
وإلا سأخصيك أيها الأمير المنحرف الذي نام مع إحدى قرينات الإمبراطور.
Xiao Wenjing, I've guarded the frontier for ten years.
شياو وينجينغ، لقد حرسْتُ الحدود لعشر سنوات.
Would you execute a meritorious minister so casually?
هل ستعدم وزيراً كفؤاً بهذه السهولة؟
Where is Lu Zhen'er?
أين لو زينير؟
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني،
the frontier will descend into chaos.
ستنزلق الحدود إلى الفوضى.
Beizhao has more than one general.
لدى بيزهاو أكثر من جنرال واحد.
We don't need you to safeguard Beizhao's peace.
لسنا بحاجة إليك لحماية سلام بيتشاو.
Go ahead and kill me if you dare.
اقتلني إن كنت تجرؤ.
Guards!
حراس!
- Yes!
- نعم!
Take Prince Rui to the dungeon.
اصطحب الأمير روي إلى الزنزانة.
Do you know who I am?
هل تعرف من أنا؟
This is utterly defiant!
هذا تحدٍّ صارخ!
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
I give you three days.
أعطيك ثلاثة أيام.
After three days, if I don't see you,
إذا لم أرك بعد ثلاثة أيام،
prepare to collect Xiao Yicheng's corpse.
استعدوا لجمع جثة شياو ييتشنغ.
Absurd! Utterly absurd!
سخيف! سخيف للغاية!
Take him away.
خذوه بعيداً.
Fu An,
فو آن,
still no news of Lu Zhen'er?
لا جديد حتى الآن بخصوص لو تشن إير؟
Your Majesty, not yet.
جلالة الملك، ليس بعد.
I forgot.
لقد نسيت.
Lu Zhen'er would rejoice if Xiao Yicheng died.
سوف يفرح Lu Zhen'er إذا مات Xiao Yicheng.
She wouldn't risk her life for him.
لن تخاطر بحياتها من أجله.
Go find Yindan.
اذهب وابحث عن يندان.
Yes.
نعم.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحية طيبة يا صاحب الجلالة.
Rise.
يعلو.
Yindan,
من يين،
do you know Empress Dowager Chen is seeking Lu Zhen'er
هل تعلم أن الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين تبحث عن لو تشن إير؟
due to the Cold Palace incident?
بسبب حادثة القصر البارد؟
She will come out for you.
ستخرج من أجلك.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
I don't know where Her Highness is.
لا أعرف أين صاحبة السمو.
Will you help me find Lu Zhen'er?
هل ستساعدني في العثور على لو تشن إير؟
I won't kill her.
لن أقتلها.
I sought you out
لقد بحثت عنك
only to find her before Empress Dowager Chen does.
ليجدها قبل أن تجدها الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين.
If she falls into Empress Dowager Chen's hands first,
إذا وقعت في قبضة الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين أولاً،
she will certainly die.
ستموت حتماً.
Without your help,
بدون مساعدتك،
she can't escape the imperial city.
لا تستطيع الهروب من المدينة الإمبراطورية.
She'll be found eventually.
سيتم العثور عليها في النهاية.
Will Your Majesty truly spare Her Highness?
هل ستعفو جلالتكم حقاً عن صاحبة السمو؟
I will.
أنا سوف.
At least this time,
على الأقل هذه المرة،
I won't kill her.
لن أقتلها.
What should I do, Your Majesty?
ماذا عليّ أن أفعل يا جلالة الملك؟
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
- (Xiao Wenjing,) - Let me go!
(شياو ون جينغ) - دعني أذهب!
(you threaten me with Yindan?)
(هل تهددني باليندان؟)
(How treacherous!)
(يا له من غدر!)
Please announce me. I seek His Majesty.
أرجو أن تعلن عني. أنا أسعى إلى جلالة الملك.
Consort Lu?
كونسورت لو؟
Your Highness, I've been expecting you.
صاحب السمو، كنت أنتظرك.
Please follow me inside.
تفضل بالدخول معي.
Maybe she hasn't seen you today.
ربما لم ترك اليوم.
Her Highness may not come out for me.
قد لا تخرج صاحبة السمو من أجلي.
She will.
ستفعل.
You go first.
ابدأ أنت أولاً.
Continue tomorrow.
نواصل غداً.
Yes.
نعم.
Where are you, Lu Zhen'er?
أين أنت يا لو زينير؟
Lu Zhen'er, does this place look familiar?
لو تشن إر، هل يبدو هذا المكان مألوفاً؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
You schemed against me and sent people to catch me in adultery.
لقد تآمرت ضدي وأرسلت الناس ليقبضوا عليّ متلبساً بالزنا.
I'll repay you in kind.
سأرد لك الجميل بالمثل.
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
who do you think sent me to harm you?
من تظن أنه أرسلني لأؤذيك؟
Enjoy yourself here.
استمتع بوقتك هنا.
I'll finally sleep with the emperor's woman.
سأنام أخيراً مع عشيقة الإمبراطور.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
let us brothers serve you well tonight.
دعونا نحن الإخوة نخدمكم جيداً هذه الليلة.
Go away!
يبتعد!
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You coward!
يا جبان!
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Lu Zhen'er? Lu Zhen'er?
لو زينير؟ لو زينير؟
Lu Zhen'er?
لو زينير؟
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Lu Zhen'er, you...
لو زينير، أنت...
Lu Zhen'er, what are you doing?
لو تشن إر، ماذا تفعلين؟
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
You? Kill me?
أنت؟ تقتلني؟
Lu Zhen'er!
لو زينير!
Let go!
اتركه!
What are you, a dog?
ما أنت، كلب؟
Like heck I am!
لا، أنا كذلك!
Lu Zhen'er, what's with you?
لو تشن إر، ما بكِ؟
I never imagined you'd collude with the Empress Dowager
لم أتخيل أبداً أنك ستتواطأ مع الإمبراطورة الأرملة
to do something this vile.
أن يفعل شيئاً بهذه الدناءة.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
The nonsense about chastity?
الهراء المتعلق بالعفة؟
I couldn't care less.
لا يهمني الأمر بتاتاً.
It's just a flesh vessel.
إنه مجرد وعاء من لحم ودم.
You think that can break me?
أتظن أن هذا سيحطمني؟
Dream on!
استمر في الحلم!
What nonsense are you spouting?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتفوه به؟
I won't trust you anymore.
لن أثق بك بعد الآن.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
ليس لدي أدنى فكرة عما تتحدث عنه.
Whether you did it or not,
سواء فعلت ذلك أم لا،
show me your remaining tricks!
أرني حيلك المتبقية!
I want to see
أريد أن أرى
how low you'll sink.
إلى أي مدى ستنحدر.
Apart from using Yindan to lure you out,
بصرف النظر عن استخدام يندان لإغراءك بالخروج،
I've done nothing else.
لم أفعل أي شيء آخر.
Have you or haven't you?
هل فعلت ذلك أم لم تفعله؟
It's just your words.
إنها مجرد كلماتك.
I'll never trust a snake like you again.
لن أثق بثعبان مثلك مرة أخرى.
Believe what you want.
صدق ما تشاء.
Where is Yindan?
أين يندان؟
I want to see her.
أريد أن أراها.
Your Majesty, it's bad.
يا صاحب الجلالة، الأمر سيء.
Miss Yindan has gone missing.
اختفت الآنسة يندان.
What?
ماذا؟
Didn't I order you to protect her?
ألم آمرك بحمايتها؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
I did assign guards to protect her, Your Majesty.
لقد قمت بتعيين حراس لحمايتها يا جلالة الملك.
But Miss Yindan said she needed the privy,
لكن الآنسة يندان قالت إنها بحاجة إلى المرحاض،
and then she vanished.
ثم اختفت.
Meaning what?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
What do you mean 'vanished'?
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "اختفى"؟
We searched the privy
فتشنا المرحاض
and nearby.
وفي الجوار.
No trace of her.
لم يُعثر لها على أي أثر.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
It must be Chen Wanyi. I'm confronting her.
لا بد أنها تشين وان يي. سأواجهها.
I'll take you.
سآخذك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Where is Yindan?
أين يندان؟
How dare you barge into Wanchun Hall unannounced!
كيف تجرؤ على اقتحام قاعة وانشون دون سابق إنذار!
Have you no respect for order?
ألا تحترم النظام؟
I am the order!
أنا الأمر!
Where is Yindan?
أين يندان؟
Ridiculous!
سخيف!
You lose your maid and demand answers from me?
أفقدتِ خادمتكِ وتطالبينني بإجابات؟
How should I know?
كيف لي أن أعرف؟
You!
أنت!
Mother, hand her over.
يا أمي، سلميها لي.
I've never met any 'Yindan.'
لم أقابل قط أي شخص يُدعى "يندان".
If you refuse,
إذا رفضت،
I'll exhume Father's coffin from the imperial mausoleum
سأقوم باستخراج نعش أبي من الضريح الإمبراطوري
and feed his bones to dogs.
ويطعم عظامه للكلاب.
Xiao Wenjing, you wouldn't dare!
شياو وينجينغ، لن تجرؤ!
I dare anything.
أنا أجرؤ على فعل أي شيء.
I'll count to three.
سأعدّ حتى ثلاثة.
If you won't free Yindan,
إذا لم تطلقوا سراح يندان،
I'll dig the grave myself.
سأحفر القبر بنفسي.
One.
واحد.
You're bluffing.
أنت تخدع.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Halt!
وقف!
You wretch!
يا لك من بائس!
My patience wears thin, Mother.
لقد نفد صبري يا أمي.
Any more nonsense,
أي هراء آخر،
and regardless of your choice,
وبغض النظر عن اختيارك،
I guarantee
أضمن لك ذلك
Father's corpse gets desecrated.
تم تدنيس جثة الأب.
Lu Zhen'er escaped.
هرب لو زينير.
Someone had to replace her.
كان لا بد من استبدالها.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
everything that happened to your maid today
كل ما حدث لخادمتك اليوم
is your fault.
هذا خطأك.
Lu Zhen'er!
لو زينير!
No!
لا!
Go away! Go!
ارحل! اذهب!
Help!
يساعد!
No!
لا!
Stop!
قف!
Spare us, Your Majesty!
ارحمنا يا جلالة الملك!
Take her away.
خذها بعيداً.
Mercy!
رحمة!
Have mercy!
ارحمنا!
♪Spring comes late after the snow♪
يأتي الربيع متأخراً بعد الثلج.
♪Having endured sorrow and joy♪
بعد أن تحملنا الحزن والفرح
♪Wandering the streets, the story unfinished♪
أتجول في الشوارع، والقصة لم تكتمل.
♪Turning around, I lost you♪
عندما استدرت، فقدتُ أثرك.
♪Separated by the dust of the past♪
يفصل بينهما غبار الماضي.
♪Our reunion veiled by moonlight♪
لقاؤنا محجوب بضوء القمر؟
♪Grant me indifference or tenderness♪
أرجو أن تمنحني اللامبالاة أو الحنان.
♪Crowds push past, brushing shoulders♪
???تتدافع الحشود، وتتلامس الأكتاف؟؟؟
♪Love grows wild within the soul♪
ينمو الحبّ بعنفٍ في أعماق الروح.
♪Longing weaves into a net♪
الشوق ينسج في شبكة.
♪Dare not speak, dare not gaze♪
لا تجرؤ على الكلام، لا تجرؤ على النظر.
♪Yet I crave your glance♪
ومع ذلك، أتوق إلى نظرتك.
♪Time, leaving many pasts behind♪
الزمن، تاركاً وراءه الكثير من الماضي.
♪Desolation follows splendor♪
الخراب يتبع المجد
♪Only after seeing enough worldly absurdity♪
فقط بعد رؤية ما يكفي من سخافات الدنيا؟
♪Will I kiss your face♪
هل سأقبل وجهك؟
♪Never forgotten, hope you've been well♪
لن ننساك أبدًا، أتمنى أن تكون بخير.
♪Borrowing the first ray of spring light♪
استعارة أول شعاع من ضوء الربيع؟
♪Can it bring about for us?♪
هل يمكن أن يحقق لنا ذلك؟
♪One look back, lasting till the end of time♪
نظرة واحدة إلى الوراء، تدوم إلى نهاية الزمان.
♪Love grows wild within the soul♪
ينمو الحبّ بعنفٍ في أعماق الروح.
♪Longing weaves into a net♪
الشوق ينسج في شبكة.
♪Dare not speak, dare not gaze♪
لا تجرؤ على الكلام، لا تجرؤ على النظر.
♪Yet I crave your glance♪
ومع ذلك، أتوق إلى نظرتك.
♪Time, leaving many pasts behind♪
الزمن، تاركاً وراءه الكثير من الماضي.
♪Desolation follows splendor♪
الخراب يتبع المجد
♪Only after seeing enough worldly absurdity♪
فقط بعد رؤية ما يكفي من سخافات الدنيا؟
♪Will I kiss your face♪
هل سأقبل وجهك؟